abroy.com 2017-12-30

# Play Free Games : Arcades, Puzzle, Adventures, Escape, Strategy, Hidden objects and Casino games online

Abroy.com PRIVACY POLICY

**1\. General**

1.1. This is the official Privacy and Policy for Abroy.com. Abroy.com can be used in this Privacy Policy as ”Abroy“, “site”, “we”, “us” or “our”.

1.3. Under 13 visitors/users will need parent or guardian’s consent before registering or providing any personal information to us.

**2\. Collection and Use of Personal Information**

2.1. Abroy.com uses any personal information available for us to respond to our visitors/costumers inquiry or comments. Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

2.2. Abroy.com may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you: register with us, or when you send questions or comments via e-mail to Abroy.com. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address.

2.3. Abroy.com may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

2.4. Other non-personal information collected by Abroy.com is in the form of logs – files that record website activity, including how many “hits” a particular web page is getting. These entries enable Abroy.com to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, track interest in purchase behavior, and troubleshoot technical concerns.

2.5. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain demographic information such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using and the domain name of your Internet service provider.

**3\. Links to third party’s and responsibilities**

3.1. To provide relevant information not found on our website, Abroy.com may provide links from our site to third party websites and we encourage our users to read third party sites privacy policies before submitting personal information. All the downloads and Exe files provided on this site are from a 3rd party and Abroy.com is not responsible for any files or adware that gets installed by their games and screensavers. They contain several adware products so download and install at your own risk. Abroy.com resumes no responsibility.

3.2. Abroy.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites. Abroy.com hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

**4\. Cookies and other aggregate data**

4.1. Abroy.com may use cookies to improve the use of our website. A “cookie” is a small file that websites often store on a user’s computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites.

4.2. The Site may contain advertisements, references and links to other websites and organizations. We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on the site and our web-based newsletters or other communications which you may choose to receive. Often these third party advertisers employ cookie and web bug technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other websites you encounter on the internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not ours. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your Personal Information.

4.3. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third party advertiser or ad server may collect from you. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions directly of them in this regard. Use of Advertisers’ tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. For more information about these third party servers and how to “opt out” of the ad-serving cookie, please click here

**5\. Privacy of Your Postings**

5.1. Abroy.com reserves the right to monitor, edit and disclose your use of the site or confidential personal information to a third party, if we believe such action is required by law or is necessary to protect and defend our rights, to enforce this Privacy Policy or the terms of the Terms of Service Agreement, or to protect the interests of our users, advertisers, service providers and others.

**6\. Protection of Personal Information**

6.1. Abroy.com maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality. However, for most internet sites or services, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access communications over an unsecured line. Abroy.com are liable for any leaks caused by us, however we do not take responsibility for unlawful intercepts or accesses what can not be protected against on reasonable standards.

**7\. Phishing**

7.1. Phishers use spoofed e-mails to lead visitor/consumers to counterfeit websites designed to trick recipients into divulging Personal Information such as account usernames and passwords. Abroy.com do not send emails asking you to provide or confirm personal information or your username or password. If somebody is asking these things form you or you receive such an email, please forward it to the site’s Privacy Policy e-mail support@abroy.com and delete the fraudulent e-mail.

**8\. Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA)**

8.1. Online behavioral advertising (“OBA”) and/or multi-site advertising on Abroy.com is occurring.

8.2. Abroy.com may use cookies to improve the use of our website. A “cookie” is a small file that websites often store on a user’s computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites.

8.3. The Site may contain advertisements, references and links to other websites and organizations. We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on the site and our web-based newsletters or other communications which you may choose to receive. Often these third party advertisers employ cookie and web bug technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other websites you encounter on the internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not ours. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your Personal Information.

8.4. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third party advertiser or ad server may collect from you. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions directly of them in this regard. Use of Advertisers’ tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. For more information about these third party servers and how to “opt out” of the ad-serving cookie. Here is the link to opt-out page on the NAI’s (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>) consumer website – [http://www.valueclickmedia.com/about/privacy](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml)

**9\. Information and questions**

9.1. If you have questions or need more information about this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use or share your Personal Information, you may contact us directly by sending an email to support@abroy.com.

**10\. Validity of the Privacy Policy**

10.1. This Privacy Policy document is the sole statement of the Abroy.com site and no other version of the Privacy Policy statement in any other form is valid. Abroy.com reserves the right to modify Privacy Policy at any time.

10.2. This Privacy Policy was last modified on the 25th of May, 2010 and is effective immediately.

2012 Abroy.com - All Rights Reserved
